{
    "subject": "Madeleine_Stowe",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Brian_Benben",
    "human_readable": "Madeleine Stowe is married to Brian Benben.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9296448230743408,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Madeleine Stowe and Brian Benben?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8905355334281921,
            "question": "Who is Madeleine Stowe married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8787854313850403,
            "question": "Is Brian Benben married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8150519132614136,
            "question": "Name a famous actor who is married to Brian Benben."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47125717997550964,
            "question": "What is Madeleine Stowe's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28474321961402893,
            "question": "Are there any famous movies that Madeleine Stowe has starred in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2212192714214325,
            "question": "Has Brian Benben won any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.218010812997818,
            "question": "What are some of Brian Benben's most popular roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05328543856739998,
            "question": "Can you name any notable couples in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03774455934762955,
            "question": "Who are some well-known actors?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Madeleine Stowe is married to Brian Benben.",
            "html": "yago_3955_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any notable couples in the entertainment industry?",
            "html": "yago_3955_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Brian Benben's most popular roles?",
            "html": "yago_3955_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Brian Benben won any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "yago_3955_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3955_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Madeleine Stowe is married to Brian Benben.\" Multiple sources indicate their marriage, with details such as the year of marriage (1982 or 1986 depending on the source), and mention of their daughter May Theodora."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}